Whoever has the money has the power.
The Lookout is a crime, drama, thriller film directed by Scott Frank.
Chris is a once promising high school athlete whose life is
turned upside down following a tragic accident.
As he tries to maintain a normal life, he takes a job as a janitor at a bank,
where he ultimately finds himself caught up in a planned heist.
Chris Pratt, played by Joseph Gordon-Levitt.
Lewis, played by Jeff Daniels.
Gary Spargo, played by Matthew Goode.
Luvlee, played by Isla Fisher.
Janet, played by Carla Gugino.
Robert Pratt, played by Bruce McGill.
The Lookout is a 2007 American crime film written and directed by Scott Frank, in his directorial debut, and
starring Joseph Gordon-Levitt, Jeff Daniels, Matthew Goode, Bruce McGill, and Isla Fisher.
The film was released by Miramax Films on March 30, 2007.
While it received positive reviews the film was nevertheless a box-office
bomb, grossing $5.4 million against a $16 million budget.
The film explores themes of mentally disabled, robbery,
bank robber, car crash, bank robbery.
The tone is emotional and intense.